ANURAG TRIPATHI

Mobile No.: +91 9624517824 Email: eranuragtripathi.10@gmail.com

OBJECTIVE:

To attain a position in the field where my knowledge and interest will have valuable application. I have more than 5 years of experience in the computer field and ability to solve technical problems and capability to take a quick decision which should help me to participate in your reputed organization.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY:

Organization: Shalby Multi Specialty Hospitals

Position: Radiology Executive Period: July 2021 to till date

- Guiding patients about precautions to be taken as per the tests prescribed to patients in person and on the telephone.
- Thoroughly checking of posting regarding payments of OPD.
- Synchronization between doctors, technicians and patients.
- Attending calls regarding queries/reports/appointments.
- Scheduling of appointments for patients.
- Timely mailing of reports to patients.
- Material indent: Procurement of supplies as per requirement.

Organization: Shreyas Foundation (Experimental School)

Position: Computer Data Entry Operator

Period: December 2015 to July 2021

- Entering valuable data in Microsoft word and excel and maintaining accurate records of schools information.
- Compile, verify accuracy and sort information according to priorities to prepare source data for computer entry.
- Review data for deficiencies or errors, correct any incompatibilities if possible and check output.
- Respond to queries for information and access relevant files.
- Scan Documents and print files.

I also helped in the H.R. Department as follow.

- Maintain the HR files such as employee's personal files, recruitment file, and E.P.F. related documents.
- Maintaining attendance software.
- Assisting in salary audit.
- Making a salary sleep & salary certificate.
- Active UAN number, issuing E.P.F. passbook & P.F. related work.

Organization: Convent English School

Position: Computer Teacher

Period: December 2012 to May 2015

- Teaching students to use computers.
- Develops and updates curriculum for the classroom.
- Downloading any important software updates.
- Organize, maintain and manage computer lab in proper working condition and keeps an inventory of supplies.
- Ensures that computer equipment is functioning properly.
- Helping students and staff members troubleshoot any technical issues.

EDUCATION QUALIFICATION:

Degree	Year	Institute/University	Percentage
B.C.A.	2013	Bholabhai Patel Collage of Computer Studies	49.70%
H.S.C.	2010	Upasana Vidhya Vihar	57.43%
S.S.C	2008	Upasana Vidhya Vihar	46%

COMPUTER PROFICIENCY:

- Capable to understand computer related problems.
- Programming Language skills such as HTML, C Language, and Java Script.
- Basic knowledge of Linux OS and their commands, Shell Scripts.
- Database like Microsoft Access, Base, and Oracle.
- Creating new users & granting rights and permissions; applying group policy on the server.
- Maintaining data backup for the end-users.
- Installation of all types of Windows-based OS and their Software.

PERSONAL DOSSIER:

Name : Anurag Mahendrakumar Tripathi

Date of Birth : 10th January 1992

Sex : Male

Language Known : Hindi, Gujarati and English

Hobbies : Reading books, poems, newspapers articles etc....

Present Address : Block B-202, Reghav Residency, Near G.E.B. Power

House, Nava Naroda - 382330, Ahmedabad

Nationality : Indian

DECLARTION:

I do hereby declare that all the information given above is true to the best of my knowledge and belief.

Anurag Tripathi Place: Ahmedabad